A Guide to the Withers Papers (Chitwood Collection), 1881-1943, Undated.
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
Withers Papers (Chitwood Collection) 1881-1943
Special Collections, Kegley Library
2006.7
52 folders.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Ruth Ann Chitwood in 2001 as part of the W. R. Chitwood Collection.
Biographical Information
Robert Enoch Withers
Robert Enoch Withers, son of Robert Walter Withers and Susan Dabney Alexander Withers, was born on 18 September 1821 at Rock Castle in Campbell County, Virginia. Withers followed his father's footsteps by becoming a physician; he graduated from the University of Virginia with a medical degree and trained at the Baltimore Almshouse Hospital.
He married Mary Virginia Royall on 3 February 1846; she was the daughter of Joseph Edwin Royall and Mary Elizabeth Royall of Lynchburg, Virginia. The young couple settled in Campbell County where he practiced medicine. During their sojourn in that county, Mary Virginia Royall Withers and Robert Enoch Withers had six daughters including Elizabeth Royall Withers (1846-1927), Susan Dabney Withers (1848-1924), Alice Chinn Withers (1850-1892), Jennett Ann Withers (1851-1945), Mary Virginia Withers (1853-1855), Josephine Withers (1854-1956), and Kate Massie Withers (1856-1911).
Faced with limited educational opportunities for his growing family, Withers accepted the advice of his cousin, Dr. Edward D. Withers, and moved to Danville, Virginia in August 1858. He joined the practice of his cousin, sent his girls to school at the female seminary run by Rev. Dame, and purchased a house on Wilson Street. Children born in Danville include Betty Ellison Withers (1858-1918), Willie Clare Withers (1859-1939), Virginia Secessia Withers (1861-1939), Robert Edwin Withers (1865-1952), and Mary Thornhill Withers (1867-1874).
When the Civil War erupted in 1861, Robert Enoch Withers joined the Confederate Army as a major; he later became colonel of the 18th Virginia Infantry Regiment until he was wounded at the Battle of Gaines Mill. He subsequently oversaw Confederate prisons and hospitals at Danville, Virginia until the end of the war.
Withers served as lieutenant-governor of Virginia in 1873. In 1875 he served as a U. S. Senator for one term. In 1885 President Grover Cleveland appointed him as U. S. Consul to Hong Kong. Withers and some of his family members, including Robert Edwin Withers, journeyed to Hong Kong where they stayed for four years.
Withers moved to Wytheville, Virginia in 1879 and eventually purchased the Ingleside home which his daughter Bettie Ellison Putney later purchased from family members. Robert Edwin Withers Sr. later bought Ingleside from Josephine Putney Dame. After his retirement from politics, Withers remained active in the Episcopal Church and served as Examiner of Records from 1896 to 1907. He died on 21 September 1907.
Robert Edwin Withers Sr.
The eleventh child and only son of Mary Virginia Royall Withers and Robert Enoch Withers, Robert Edwin Withers Sr. was born 13 March 1865 in Danville, Virginia. He attended private schools and the Virginia Military Institute in 1882. At V.M.I. Withers joined Sigma Chi fraternity. After his graduation in 1885, he served as secretary to his father who was U. S. Consul to Hong Kong.
Withers moved to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania in 1893 and began a long career at the Pittsburgh Reduction Company which later became the Aluminum Company of America. He served as treasurer and assistant secretary, vice-president of finance, a director, and as senior vice-president.
He married Mary Cloyd Kent on 2 June 1892. The couple had two sons, Robert Edwin Withers Jr. who was born on 1 June 1894 and Kent Cloyd Withers who was born on 28 December 1910.
As his father, Robert Edwin Withers was an active member of the Episcopal Church. He served as a lay reader and vestry member of Calvary Episcopal Church in Pittsburgh for many years.
Withers and his wife purchased Ingleside from Josephine Putney Dame and spent many summers with family members there. Robert Edwin Withers died on 29 December 1952.
Robert Edwin Withers Jr.
Robert Edwin Withers Jr. was born on 1 June 1894. Suffering from various physical and behavior problems, he attended a sanitarium and school run by Dr. Mary Pogue at Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. He graduated from Yeates Preparatory School in Lancaster, Pennsylvania in 1916 and attended the University of Virginia. When the United States entered World War I, Withers enlisted as a private in the Marine Corps and served guard duty at Grieve, France as a sharpshooter.
He graduated from the University of Pittsburgh in 1922 with a B. S. in economics. He studied under Rev. W. A. R. Goodwin at the College of William and Mary in 1927 and the following year entered the Virginia Seminary in Alexandria, Virginia to study for the Episcopal priesthood. he was ordained at Emmanuel Church, Glenmore, Buckingham County, Virginia in July 1931. He served several parishes in Appomattox, Buckingham, and Cumberland counties and also in Ridgeland and Bluffton, South Carolina.
Robert Edwin Withers Jr. married Frances Glover Haskin son 10 August 1933. Haskins was a schoolteacher and a native of Buckingham County. They had one daughter, Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, who was born on 28 October 1935. Robert Edwin Withers died in February 1981 and Frances Withers died in October 1989.
Scope and Content
Dr. W. Randolph Chitwood evidently acquired this collection at an estate sale. This collection complements the Withers Family Papers (Mss. Collection 1997.1) donated by Gary and Ann Laing in 1997. This collection is distinguished from the Laing collection as Withers Papers (Chitwood Collection).
The collection consists of the following series: Series I, Correspondence (1899-1943, undated) includes letters to and from Robert Enoch Withers, Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Robert Edwin Withers Jr., and Mary Cloyd Kent Withers.
Series II, Examiner of Records to the Auditor of Public Accounts - Correspondence (1900-1907) contains correspondence of Robert Enoch Withers who served as Examiner of Records for the 15th Judicial District of Virginia from 1896 to 1907. As such Withers reported and audited claims and debts against the Commonwealth of Virginia for Bland, Carroll, Pulaski, Smyth, Tazewell, and Wythe counties. The series include correspondence from guardians, executors, commissioners, and others managing estates or orphans as required by an 4 March 1896 of the General Assembly to report income and personal property.
Series III, Literary Drafts - Word Sketches (Undated), contains drafts and research notes by Mary Cloyd Kent Withers for her booklet Word Sketches of Some of Her Relatives. Series IV, Books (1881, Undated), contains a ledger and a copy of Myers Tactics; the Templar Manual. Series V, Photographs (Undated), contains five photographs while Series VI, Miscellaneous Records (1938, 1942), contains material relating to the Aluminum Company of America and Virginia Military Institute.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence. 1899-1943, Undated, 9 folders.
  - Folder 1. Correspondence - Robert Enoch Withers and Mary Virginia Royall Withers. 1899-1900., 6 items.
    - Letter. Elizabeth Royall Withers Carter, Evansville, Indiana to Robert Enoch Withers, Wytheville, Virginia. 7 June 1899., 4 p. (Folder-item 1:1)
      She requests that he persuade Bishop Randolph to transfer her husband, Rev. Edwin Lewis Carter, to parish of Holy Innocents.
    - Letter. Susan C. Massie, Three Springs, Nelson County, Virginia to Robert Enoch Withers, Wytheville, Virginia. 9 September 1899., 3 p. (Folder-item 1:2)
      Re: his recommendation for treating her dog for scratches, remarriage of Henry Cook (first husband of Jennett Ann Withers), and family news.
    - Letter. Flora Virginia Withers Withers, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Enoch Withers, Wytheville, Virginia. 16 January 1900., 4 p. (Folder-item 1:3)
      Re: illness of their brother, Henry Howard Withers, and family news.
    - Letter. Richard Hodges, Norfolk, Virginia to Mary Virginia Royall Withers. 11 February 1900., 1 p. (Folder-item 1:4)
      Re: Christmas present.
    - Letter. American Biographical Publishing Company, Chicago, Illinois to Robert Enoch Withers, Wytheville, Virginia. 20 March 1900., 1 p. (Folder-item 1:5)
      Re: request that he review biographical sketch.
    - Letter. Raleigh W. Chinn Sr., Dumont, Colorado to Robert Enoch Withers, Wytheville, Virginia. 3 April 1900., 2 p. (Folder-item 1:6)
      Re: genealogy of the Chinn family and ties to Withers family through Jennett Chinn and Enoch K. Withers.
  - Folder 2. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Sr.. 1918-1943., 5 letters.
    - Telegram. G. R. Gibbons, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Sr.. 15 May 1918., 1 p. (Folder-item 2:1)
      Re: arrival of Robert Edwin Withers Jr. in Brooklyn on 14 May 1918 and subsequent departure for Marine Corps training at Parris Island.
    - Telegram. T. C. Treadwell, Colonel, United States Marine Corps, Parris Island, South Carolina to Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 17 August 1918., 1 p. (Folder-item 2:2)
      Re: active duty status of Robert Edwin Withers Jr.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Co. L, 3rd Battalion, 11th Regiment United States Marine Corps, American Expeditionary Forces to Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 7 December 1918., 4 p. (Folder-item 2:3)
      Re: guard duty, France, camp and supply depot.
    - Letter. William G. Stanard, Corresponding Secretary and Librarian, Virginia Historical Society, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 17 December 1931., 2 p. (Folder-item 2:4)
      Re: membership in the Society.
    - Letter. Clarence Ketner, Wytheville, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 25 May 1943., 4 p. (Folder-item 2:5)
      Re: back problems of Josephine Withers Read, visit of Mary Terry, his garden, flower garden at Ingleside, and anticipation of his upcoming visit.
  - Folder 3. Correspondence. 1945, Undated., 9 letters.
    This folder contains birthday greetings to Robert Edwin Withers Sr. from Martha Anne Rogers Withers, Earl Blough, Rose Carter, Rev. Arthur B. Kinsolving, Charles H. Monritz, Robert W. Williams, W. M. Gifford, J. Howard Alger, and Mary Cloyd Kent Withers.
  - Folder 4. Correspondence - Mary Cloyd Kent Withers. 1910-1934., 6 letters.
    - Letter. Eliza Ann Patton Kent Darling to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 24 December 1910., 8 p. (Folder-item 4:1)
      Re: impending birth of Kent Cloyd Withers.
    - Telegram. Robert Edwin Withers Jr., New York, New York to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 14 May 1918., 1 p. (Folder-item 4:2)
      Re: arrival in Brooklyn and subsequent departure for non-commissioned officer training at Parris Island, South Carolina.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Jr., aboard ship Metagama, to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 1 July 1922., 4 p. (Folder-item 4:3)
      Re: European tour itinerary, lack of deck chairs, friends aboard ship, and return trip plans.
    - Letter. Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Richmond, Virginia to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 18 February 1928., 4 p. (Folder-item 4:4)
      Re: attendance of Eliza A. P. Kent Darling at wedding of Miss Griffin, her visit with Charlotte Miller Kent, and family news. Enclosures, newspaper clippings on Edwin Palmer and Randolph Harrison
    - Letter. Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Richmond, Virginia to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 21 March 1928., 4 p. (Folder-item 4:5)
      Re: marriage of Kent Crosby Darling and Nelle Powell Payne Darling, visit of Mrs. Fred Darling, and weather.
    - Letter. Elizabeth Needham, Fair Oak, West Disburgy, Manchester, England to Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 10 September 1934., 2 p. (Folder-item 4:6)
      Re: death of George Edward Darling, family news.
  - Folder 5. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1908-1910., 12 items.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Portsmouth, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 25 December 1908., 3 p. (Folder-item 5:1)
      Re: gloves, wishes for happy Christmas, visit with Catherine Hodges and Richard Hodges.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 24 May 1909., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:2)
      Re: check for birthday presents, recommendation that he purchase long pants and socks.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 6 September 1909., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:3)
      Re: description of Yellowstone National Park, hotel and wild animals.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Los Angeles, California to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 25 September 1909., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:4)
      Re: visits in California.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers. St. Louis, Missouri to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 13 October 1909., 7 p. (Folder-item 5:5)
      Re: miserable city of East St. Louis that she toured to see aluminum plant and plans to buy him clothing.
    - Letter. Mrs. J. R. Alter, Parnassus, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 1 November 1909., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:6)
      Re: football game between Parnassus and Kensington high schools, George Edward Darling and Kent Crosby Darling.
    - Letter. Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 23 November 1909., 3 p. (Folder-item 5:7)
      Re: summer trip to Europe, visits with Eliza Ann Kent Darling and Joseph Cloyd Kent, Charlotte Miller Kent and Charlotte Kent and Jane Kent.
    - Letter. Josephine Withers REad, Wytheville, Virginia to Robert Edwin withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 19 December 1909., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:8)
      Re: preparations for Christmas presents and visits, Robert Read an family, John Royall Read, and illness of Robert Read.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Parnassus, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 29 December 1909., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:9)
      Re: Christmas activities and visits.
    - Letter. Josephine Withers Read, Wytheville, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 13 July 1910., 4 p. (Folder-item 5:10)
      Re: visit of Daisie Maupin and best wishes for his upcoming trip.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., New Kensington, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Oak Leigh Sanitarium, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin. 20 October 1910., 2 p. (Folder-item 5:11.)
      Re: disappointment in his recent behavior.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1910., 3 p. (Folder-item 5:12)
      Re: her pregnancy and expected delivery in December.
  - Folder 6. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1914., 9 items.
    - Letter. Bud [unknown], Haddonfield, New Jersey to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Chelsea, New Jersey. 23 June 1914., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:1)
      Re: plans for Robert Edwin Withers Jr. to have a tutor, his college exams, and dancing lessons.
    - Letter. David J. Pearsall, Mauch Chunk, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Riverview Academy, Poughkeepsie, New York. 16 July 1914., 2 p. (Folder-item 6:2)
      Re: summer school attendance and hopes that food at Yeates School improves.
    - Letter. A. P. Jervey, Charleston, South Carolina to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 18 September 1914., 4 p. (Folder-item 6:3)
      Re: preparation for scholarship examination at Charleston College, sailing, hunting sea birds, and football team.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 26 November 1914., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:4)
      Re: problem with her ears and description of th opening of Parliament and the British royal family in letter from Eliza Ann Kent Darling.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 1 December 1915, 2 p. (Folder-item 6:5)
      Re: football game between University of Virginia and University of North Carolina played in Richmond on Thanksgiving Day, hunting birds, and congratulations on his school report card.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 7 December 1914., 4 p. (Folder-item 6:6)
      Re: family matters and preparation for Christmas.
    - Letter. Mary Cloyd Kent Withers, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 12 December 1914., 4 p. (Folder-item 6:7)
      Re: visits to various ladies, situation of her previous maid, Pearson, and family news.
    - Letter. J. J. D. Hall, Superintendent, Galilee Mission, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 21 December 1914., 1 p. (Folder-item 6:8)
      Re: appreciation for donation and encouragement to join the ministry.
    - letter. David J. Pearsall, Mauch Chunk, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 24 December 1914., 3 p. (Folder-item 6:9)
      Re: chicken pox, sledding, and Christmas parties.
  - Folder 7. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1915-1916, 1929, Undated., 7 letters.
    - Letter. Sister Anne [unknown], Newburgh, New York to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 15 October 1915., 6 p. (Folder-item 7:1)
      Re: autumn activities, opening of new Masonic Temple, and activities of friends.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 12 November 1915., 2 p. (Folder-item 7:2)
      Re: trip to North Carolina on Aluminum Company of America business, visit with Edith Bolling Galt and Woodrow Wilson, and planned visit to Wytheville.
    - Letter. Anne [unknown], Newburgh, New York to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 17 November 1915., 3 p. (Folder-item 7:3)
      Re: football games, attendance at fraternity meeting in New York City, and studies.
    - Postcard. Herbert C. Boissier, Lake Geneva, Wisconsin to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 8 December 1915., 1 p. (Folder-item 7:4)
      Re: request for biographical information for parish registry.
    - Letter. Isabel M. Alter, Wilson College, Chambersburg, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. December 1915, 4 p. (Folder-item 7:5)
      Re: examinations, visit to Mrs. Shumaker, and War Relief Dance.
    - Letter. Charlie Horr, Newark, New Jersey to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 30 December 1915., 2 p. (Folder-item 7:6)
      Re: thanks him for card.
    - Letter. Anne F. W., Newburgh, New York to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. 30 December 1915., 2 p. (Folder-item 7:7)
      Re: thanks for calendar.
  - Folder. Correspondence - Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1916, 1929, Undated, 8 items.
    - Letter. Isabel M. Alter, Wilson College, Chambersburg, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 7 February 1916., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:1)
      Re: frightful examinations, food box, and response to his invitation to dance.
    - Letter. Isabel M. Alter, Wilson College, Chambersburg, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Yeates School, Lancaster, Pennsylvania. 30 April 1916., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:2)
      Re: she declines invitation to dance, May Day activities, and play.
    - Letter. Aunt Lizzie [unknown], Charlotte, North Carolina to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 4 June 1916., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:3)
      Re: congratulations on graduation and World War I.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 12 June 1916., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:4)
      Re: repair of automobile on their way home from his graduation and arrival of Kent Crosby Darling and George Edward Darling.
    - Letter. Robert Edwin Withers Sr., Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 17 December 1916., 2 p. (Folder-item 8:5)
      Re: visit to relatives in Danville.
    - Letter. Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr., Charlottesville, Virginia. 18 December 1916., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:6)
      Re: visit to Richmond and his examinations.
    - Letter. Anastasia Pleasants Smith Kent, Richmond, Virginia to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. 1 January 1929., 2 p. (Folder-item 8:7)
      Re: thank you for book, wedding of George Edward Darling.
    - Letter. Kent Crosby Darling, London, England to Robert Edwin Withers Jr. Undated., 3 p. (Folder-item 8:8)
      Re: sailing his boat at Kensington Gardens.
  - Folder 9. Correspondence. 1929, Undated., 2 items.
    This folder contains a letter from Bertha Frances Fisher to Kent Cloyd Withers and a letter from Ellen B. Stuart to Eliza Ann Kent Darling.
- Series II. Examiner of Records to the Auditor of Public Accounts - Correspondence. 1900-1907, 30 folders.
  - Folder 1. Correspondence - Bland County. 1903., 1 item. (Series-folder 2:1)
    This folder contains letter from L. M. Shrader of Rocky Gap who was administrator of an unknown estate.
  - Folder 2. Correspondence - Carroll County. 1900, 1903, 1906, 4 items. (Series-folder 2:2)
    This folder contains letters re: C. C. Smith, administrator of estate of J. P. Smith, Hillsville; H. R. Bishop and W. R. Bishop, administrators of estate of J. S. Bishop, Wolf Glade; and Joseph S. Byrd, administrator of estate of S. F. Byrd, Fries; N. P. Oglesby, counselor in Thomas vs. Thomas, Bristol.
  - Folder 3. Correspondence - Carroll County. 10 April 1907 - 11 April 1907., 8 items. (Series-folder 2:3)
    This folder contains letters re: F. P. Branscome, administrator of the estate of S. C. Scott, Laurel Fork; Mrs. S. E. Burcham, guardian of Charles Branscome and Willie Branscome, children of S. E. Burcham, Pipers Gap; B. F. Calaway and L. A. Houseman, committee for W. S. Blair, Galax; Burrell Smith, guardian of Melissa Bolen and Emmet Bolen, Laurel Fork; Lawson Worrell, commissioner for Lena Nestor vs. James Nestor and administrator of the estate of James A. Vaughan, Hillsville; D. C. Combs, guardian of Rosa Vernon and Wiley Vernon, Max; Justin McGraw, administrator of estate of J. Hampton McGraw, Cana; and C. M. Marshall, administrator of estate of Samuel M. Stanley, Stone Mountain.
  - Folder 4. Correspondence - Carroll County. 12 April 1907 - 15 April 1907., 7 items. (Series-folder 2:4)
    This folder contains letters re: S. W. Tompkins, commissioner for Lena Utt vs. Arthur Utt et al, Hillsville; George Quesenberry, guardian of Isaac Webb and Sanford Webb, Peck; B. F. Calaway, administrator of estate of F. W. Givens, Galax; A. W. Hylton, administrator of estate of J. C. Duncan, Peck; R. E. Jones, guardian of Cora Lee Jones, Galax; Jacob Nester, guardian of Isaac Webb and Sanford Lee Webb, Hillsville; and Mary E. Vinson, guardian of Roy Vinson, Martha L. Vinson, and Robert E. Vinson, Hillsville.
  - Folder 5. Correspondence - Carroll County. 16 April 1907 - 19 April 1907, 7 items. (Series-folder 2:5)